DENITSA PESHEVA

dpessheva@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/denitsa-pesheva-94037a105/ 😱 github.com/Dpessheva



Junior Software Developer

Professional background

I switched to web development in 2018. My interest is in the field of front-end development. For a year, I have attended various courses in an online academy for programming. After that, I have started gaining real working experience as a junior web developer. During the last year, I have built a good basis of knowledge and, I want to continue growing and learning.

Key Competencies & Offerings

- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS

- NodeJS
- Express
- Angular
- React
- Yup

- Scrum
- Visual Studio code
- Jest
- Github
- Soft Skills

- Emotional intelligence
- Quick learner
- Self-starter
- Team player
- Good communication skills

Selected work experience

Feb 2020 - Sept 2020

Junior Front-end developer

Bending the rules

As a front-end developer at Bending the rules, I was a part of a big project where I was responsible for the front-end development of the application. During the process. I have worked with React, Typescript, Jest, Yup, and Github.

- Creating separated and reusable components.
- Refactoring, bugs-fixing.
- Writing unit tests.

Jul 2019 - Jan 2020

Junior Software Developer

Zaapps, Eindhoven, the Netherlands

As a part of the development team of Zzapps, I have participated in different projects. It helped me to gain real-life experience in software development with tools like Angular, TypeScript, Firebase, NodeJs, Google could platform and a few more.

- Refactoring, bugs-fixing
- Back-end development with Nodejs and Firebase
- Front-end

Feb 2017 - Dec 2017

Data analyst internship

Effective Profiles, Gouda, the Netherlands

- Engaged in a project for identifying duplicated profiles in the database
- Engaged in a project for customers segmentation
- Reports and data visualization

Feb 2015 - March 2015 Human Resources internship Address Real Estate, Sofia Bulgaria As an intern, I was focused on: • Polls • Reports Headhunting Marketing internship March 2014 - June 2014 Getlokal, Sofia, Bulgaria • Writing website content • Brand development • Reaching new clients Education JavaScript Web Developer 2018 - 2019 Software University 2015 - 2017 Communication and Information Technology (MSc) Tilburg University Human Aspects of Information Technology 2011 - 2015 Psychology (BSc) New Bulgarian University Organizational Psychology Languages Bulgarian Native English Professional working proficiency Dutch Elementary proficiency Created with 📅 VisualCV